<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Verified Apps</string>
    <string name="app_header">Verified Apps\nby Privacy Guides</string>
    <string name="startup_tagline">Check installed apps against crowdsourced signing fingerprints.</string>
    <string name="startup_verify_apk">Verify APK file</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="view_source_code_setting_name">Source code</string>
    <string name="view_source_code_setting_description">View Verified Apps\' source code on the GitHub website in your web browser</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_setting_name">Privacy policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_setting_description">View Verified Apps\' privacy policy in app</string>
    <string name="license">License</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy policy</string>
    <string name="license_setting_name">Verified Apps License</string>
    <string name="license_setting_description">View Verified Apps\' License in app</string>
    <string name="credits">Credits</string>
    <string name="credits_setting_name">Credits</string>
    <string name="credits_setting_description">View open source licenses of code that Verified Apps uses in app</string>
    <string name="dynamic_color_setting_name">Dynamic color</string>
    <string name="dynamic_color_setting_description">Use your wallpaper colors for the app theme (Android 12 and above)</string>
    <string name="dynamic_color_setting_unavailable_description">Dynamic color requires Android 12 or newer. The app uses the default teal theme.</string>
    <string name="pitch_black_background_setting_name">Pitch black background</string>
    <string name="pitch_black_background_setting_description">Replaces background with pitch black background when dark theme is on</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="theme">Theme</string>
    <string name="full_privacy_policy" translatable="false">Privacy Policy\n\nThis app does not store any data permanently other than preferences. This app does not make network connections itself. When you choose to submit an app that is not in the internal database, the app opens your web browser to a GitHub issue form with verification fields pre-filled from data already shown on screen; submitting that form is handled by GitHub in your browser.\n\nThis app can see which apps are installed on your device for the purpose of viewing information about them and checking them against the internal database. You can share and copy verification information to other apps using the share/copy buttons. Clipboard content is only used when you tap copy; it is not read otherwise.\n\nYou can provide an apk file to this app which will be temporarily stored in this app\'s cache directory and deleted as soon as it is done processing the needed information about the apk file.\n\nLast updated: June 3, 2026.</string>
    <string name="full_license" translatable="false">MIT License\n\nCopyright (c) 2026 Jonah Aragon\nCopyright (c) 2026 Privacy Guides &amp; contributors\n\nPermission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
    of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal
    in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
    to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
    copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
    furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:\n\nThe above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all
    copies or substantial portions of the Software.\n\nTHE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
    IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
    FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
    AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
    LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
    OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE
    SOFTWARE.
    </string>
    <string name="verify_app">Verify App</string>
    <string name="verify_internal_database_status">Internal database status</string>
    <string name="app_list">App List</string>
    <string name="app_list_search">Search apps</string>
    <string name="app_list_search_hint">Search apps</string>
    <string name="app_list_search_close">Close search</string>
    <string name="navigate_up">Navigate up</string>
    <string name="app_list_results_count">%1$d apps</string>
    <string name="app_list_empty">No apps match your search or filters</string>
    <string name="app_list_sort">Sort</string>
    <string name="nav_open_apk">Open APK</string>
    <string name="app_list_sort_name_asc">Name (A–Z)</string>
    <string name="app_list_sort_name_desc">Name (Z–A)</string>
    <string name="app_list_sort_package">Package name</string>
    <string name="app_list_sort_status">Database status</string>
    <string name="app_list_filter_verified">Verified</string>
    <string name="app_list_filter_not_in_database">Unknown</string>
    <string name="app_list_filter_mismatch">Mismatch</string>
    <string name="app_list_status_verified">Verified in database</string>
    <string name="app_list_status_mismatch">Fingerprint mismatch</string>
    <string name="app_list_status_unknown">Not in database</string>
    <string name="donation">Donation</string>
    <string name="donation_setting_name">Donation</string>
    <string name="donation_setting_description">Make a donation to support Privacy Guides\' non-profit mission.</string>
    <string name="advanced">Advanced</string>
    <string name="show_hasmultiplesigners_setting_name">Show hasMultipleSigners</string>
    <string name="show_hasmultiplesigners_setting_description">"Shows hasMultipleSigners in the app verification screen. This is useful for contributing to the internal verification info database."</string>
    <string name="show_sharing_tools_setting_name">Show sharing tools</string>
    <string name="show_sharing_tools_setting_description">Shows share and copy verification info buttons on the app verification screen</string>
    <string name="nomatch_github_submit_message">It\'s possible this app is not legitimate, or this app is outdated, or our database is outdated. Please submit this fingerprint to our database, and our team will further investigate whether your copy of the app is legitimate and let you know in a reply online.</string>
    <string name="always_show_github_submit_setting_name">Always show Submit on GitHub</string>
    <string name="always_show_github_submit_setting_description">Shows the Submit on GitHub button even when the app is already in the internal database</string>
    <string name="user_apps_tab">User Apps</string>
    <string name="system_apps_tab">System Apps</string>
    <string name="show_system_apps_setting_name">Show system apps</string>
    <string name="show_system_apps_setting_description">Include pre-installed system apps in the app list. Note that many of these apps are not eligible for submission!</string>
</resources>
